http://www.premiumiv.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Premium Island Vacations respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it.
Information Collection and Use
In order for Premium Island Vacations to maintain its high standard of customer services and online facilities it is necessary to collect data from visitors on www.premiumislandvacations.com
We collect e-mail addresses and of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by our guests and visitors, such as contact information, survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used by Premium Island Vacations to contact our guest and visitors regarding villa rental availability requests they have placed online. We will only send you e-mail or mailings to inform you of updates and product information on Premium Island Vacations, if you have provided your e-mail address or mailing address to us through our website. Should you wish to opt out of receiving communications from Premium Island Vacations in the future, please let us know by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link within the e-mail that you received from us, by visiting the our website and clicking the “unsubscribe” button on the homepage, by sending us e-mail at the above address, or by writing to us at the above address..
We do not sell or rent this information to anyone. Premium Island Vacations will only share your personally identifiable information with our authorized villa service providers that perform certain services or functions on our behalf.
This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Premium Island Vacations website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.
HAND PICKED LUXURY ST BARTS VILLAS
(0059) 0 590 290 007
vip@premiumiv.com
Sign-up to our Newsletter
Sign-Up
Privacy Policy
Disclaimer
XML Sitemap
